reikirays.com 2018-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Reiki Rays

WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY for REIKIRAYS.COM

Agreeing to this policy implies that you have also read and agreed to the [Terms and Conditions](https://reikirays.com/terms-and-conditions/) and the [Legal Notice](https://reikirays.com/legal-notice/).

Our commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. The following policy explains how we deal with the information collected from you, your personal information and options available to you in regard to the policies followed by us.

Collection of your information

**REIKIRAYS.COM** **** is owned and managed by **ACORN GECKO SRL** (“the company”), a Romanian company registered under the EU VAT number RO32893426. The company is the sole owner of information collected on this website. We will not share, sell, or trade this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of data/information:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views;

(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services ;

Confidentiality of your personal information

**Collection of information**

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify the client or his company including, but not limited to, User name, telephone number, e-mail address, street address, occupation, and/or industry.

By giving personal information, the client gives the company consent to collect and use it in accordance with this agreement.

  * **Information disclosure and sharing**

While, client’s personal information is never shared outside the scope of the company’s business without prior permission, however client’s personal information may be stored and/or processed with supporting companies/services as requested.

  * ******Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. However, you are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password. Please do not share your password with others. Change your passwords regularly.

  * **Your rights**

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you as well as request that we delete this information from our records. Please use the [Contact Us](https://reikirays.com/contact/) form to get in touch.

  * ******Control of Your Passwords**

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User IDs and passwords. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your passwords to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and passwords or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party’s privacy policy. If you lose control of your passwords, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf.

  * ******Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. This will be corrected/updated within a reasonable time.

Restricted Activities

Your Information  and your activities on the Site shall not: (a) be false, inaccurate or misleading; (b) be fraudulent; (c) infringe any third party’s copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy; (d) violate any law, statute, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to, those governing export control, consumer protection, unfair competition, antidiscrimination or false advertising); (e) be defamatory, trade libelous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing; (f) be obscene or contain child pornography or, if otherwise adult in nature or harmful to minors, shall be posted only in the Mature Audiences section and shall be distributed only to people legally permitted to receive such content; (g) contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information.

License

Solely to enable the company to use the information you supply us with, so that we are not violating any rights you might have in that information, you agree to grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sub licensable (through multiple tiers) right to exercise the copyright, publicity, and database rights (but no other rights) you have in Your Information, in any media now known or not currently known, with respect to Your Information. We will only use Your Information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

Our Use of Your Information

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe trading; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our User Agreement; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site’s content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information.

We will be sending you emails containing free information (such as articles, eBooks, videos, webinars, free courses or events, documents etc) as well as promotional materials and information about products for purchase. We will be sending you, on average, one email per day.

Cookies

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We may send cookies which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.

Advertisers

We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal information and may disclose such information to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes.

Reiki Rays Community

Your User ID or name if you provide it when commenting is displayed throughout the Site and is therefore available to the public. All of your activities on the Site will be identifiable to this information. Other people may see your items that you have purchased in the past, your feedback rating and associated comments, your postings on the Site, and so on. Therefore, if you associate your name with your User ID, the people you have revealed your name to will be able to personally identify your Reiki Rays activities. _ _

Legal Requests

The company cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and Reiki Rays community from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, User ID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to: prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, address, city, postal code, country, phone number, email, and company name to other participants under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. Again, Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

Notice

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time without any notice. Please check back regularly.

Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please contact us using the Contact form on this website.

Agreeing to this policy implies that you have also read and agreed to the [Terms and Conditions](https://reikirays.com/terms-and-conditions/) and the [Legal Notice](https://reikirays.com/legal-notice/).
